Unknown Oral History Project OHP023
People's Archive, MLK Library
Unknown Oral History Project
1996-2005
People's Archive, MLK Library
OHP023
1.5 Linear feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
There is no Deed of Gift for this collection.
Oral History
- Series 1: Interviews
  Scope and Contents
  Materials in this series include master of the oral histories on audio cassette. There are duplicate copies of 23-22 and 23-23.
  - Mary Leckie, 2005 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 23-01)
  - Hortence Fitzgerald, 1996 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 23-02)
  - Inez Browne, 1997 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 23-03A)
  - Inez Browne, 1997 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 23-03B)
  - Logsdons, 2004 November (Box 1, Folder 23-04)
  - Carmen Marrero, 2004 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 23-05)
  - Ken Butler, 2004 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 23-06)
  - Richard Hardy, 2004 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 23-07)
  - Fred Hays, 2004 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 23-08)
  - Malvina Brown, 2004 December 29 (Box 1, Folder 23-09)
  - Regina Ingram, 2005 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 23-10)
  - Fred Ettes, 2005 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 23-11)
  - Gloria Mitchell, 2005 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 23-12)
  - Glady Mitchell, 2005 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 23-13A)
  - Glady Mitchell, 2005 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 23-13B)
  - Shanon Deane, 2005 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 23-14)
  - Mike Heller, 2005 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 23-15)
  - Honora Thompson, 2005 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 23-16)
  - Bill and Julia Schartzer (Box 1, Folder 23-17)
  - Tasso Vondas (Box 1, Folder 23-18)
  - Tony Grillo (Box 1, Folder 23-19A)
  - Tony Grillo (Box 1, Folder 23-19B)
  - Clarence Bates (Box 1, Folder 23-20)
  - Ben (Box 1, Folder 23-21)
  - Louise Townsend Smith (Box 1, Folder 23-22)
    General
    2 copies
  - Wolsey Semple, 2005 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 23-23)
  - Eddie Hicks (Box 1, Folder 23-24A)
  - Eddie Hicks (Box 1, Folder 23-24B)